Muhammad Noman

Address:

Flat # 403, 4th Floor, Block-B, Taj Palace, Fatima Jinnah Colony, Near Fatmi Masjid, Jamshed Road # 3, Karachi

Phone:

+923323213659

Email:

m.noman.m.nasir@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE:

To join a dynamic, progressive and growing organization for experience, enhancement of professional skills and carrier growth. Further I would like to offer my services for your institution with al lots skills and experience of existing recognized and well established financial institution.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Teaching in Famous Learning Corner Coaching Centre class for 2nd year in Mathematics, Chemistry & Physics subject till date.(2019-2020)

Teaching in Famous Learning Corner Coaching Centre class for 2nd year in Mathematics, Chemistry & Physics subject till date.(2020-2021)

Web Development Intern

Company: Orbhex (25/JUNE/2022-10/SEP/2022)

- Implemented changes to make website more successful, functional and usable.
- Deployed web capabilities to assist with data life cycle management.
- Evaluated code to verify compatibility with browsers, devices and operating systems.

Senior Frontend Developer

Company: Diligent Creators (23/JUNE/2023 - Present)

I am delighted to extend to you an offer of employment with Diligent Creators. After careful consideration of your qualifications and skills, we believe that you would be a valuable addition to our team. We are excited about the possibility of working together and contributing to the continued success of our organization.

We are excited to welcome you to the team at Diligent Creators. We believe that your skills and expertise will contribute significantly to our success. We look forward to a fruitful employment relationship.

EDUCATION:

Appearing in Bachelor of Science of Software Engineering (BSSE) at Muhammad Ali Jinnah University in Karachi.

Pre-Engineering at NCR-CET College Karachi 2019

Matriculation in Karachi Board

2017

ADDITIONAL SKILLS:

Programming: JAVA,C++, HTML,CSS,BOOTSTRAP,WEB

HOSTING, GITHUB, JAVASCRIPT, REACTJS

Microsoft Office package: Microsoft Word, Excel, Access Database operation: Microsoft Office Access, Oracle 8i

PERSONAL INFORMATION:

Father Name: Muhammad Nasir

6th October, 2000 > Date of Birth:

> CNIC # : 42301-6990634-1

➤ Martial Status : Single

Interest: My main interest reading a book & play in cricket.

REFERENCES: References available on request